I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
That's the stage where you'll
do a session with Dying Breed.
I can't believe...
that I can play with them.
We need a huge event
for Belle Ame's debut.
I'm really grateful to you.
Eiji, this is business.
That manager was just what I expected
of a manager of an 8 million-seller band.
Our talks went smoothly.
"Live 12
'Secret Live"'
Hey, is that band any good?
Of course, Eddy.
These guys are the
next big thing in Japan.
Kevin, you're pushy.
What do you think, Matt?
If we like them at the rehearsal...
yeah, we could play with them.
Come on. This is business. For me!
Hm...What are they called?
Belle Ame...It means
"beautiful spirit" in French.
Hey, Jim! Don't film me.
Bugger off. Hit the road!
Why? Why not? I should let
everyone know how smart you are.
-No. Eddy...Can you tell him not to?
-Come on, over here.
-Jim, give me that...
-Come on.
Give me that camera. I'll kick your ass.
I told you not to film.
Uh...Eddy's guests...six of us.
"Registration for Participants"
All right. Please sign here.
Awright!
Ryusuke-kun...
Hey, Koyuki!
Come on. Come at me.
Chiba-kun!
-Oh!
-Taa!
Ouch!
-I can't see...
-Koyuki!
I'm going further up front!
-Oh...He's playing with his teeth.
-They're starting with
an imitation of Jimi Hendrix?
Another minute, feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
No guarantees, but I'm so sure
She's into silence, candy for the head
Had a waking vision
I been so high ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly,
you gotta let go
Simply the most big sensation
once you're here you won't go back
She's really pretty, one-eyed vision
lose the fear it don't come back
Little sister showed me,
really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
Yeah, when I found you
My world came crashin' down
once you're here you won't go back
lose the fear it don't come back
Koyuki, do you know who that is?
Hmm...Is he a musician?
He's the movie director Jim Walsh-
28 years old.
He's a brilliant filmmaker from New York.
Why's he here?
He's shooting Dying Breed's tour.
I'd like to introduce our
special guest who just came in.
Mr. Eiji Kimura.
I'm finally here...
Hey! You really sucked at the rehearsal.
My Strat!
Your music won't save anybody.
Fuck off!
Hey, hey...They don't understand
the situation right here.
What'cha gonna do now, Eddy?
-Huh?!
-Come on!
Matt's calling you, Koyuki.
All right. You gotta sing with us.
Hey, look!
-Who's that?
-He's Japanese.
He's still a kid!
Hey, what'cha gonna play, dude?
Koyuki, what's your
favorite song of Dying Breed?
He's asking what your favorite song is!
Moon on the Water...
because I have special memory...
Full moon sways
Gentl...
What was that?
A Matt's joke or something?
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day
On my way
Looking for a moment with my dear
Full moon waves
Slowly on the surface of the lake
You were there
Smiling in my arms for all those years
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
Well, I don't blame him.
He got up on the stage
with Dying Breed, after all.
But it's been a week.
A guitar expresses personality
through its six strings.
Come on, Ryusuke...Say it in English.
Listen, Koyuki! You already had me
say it a hundred times. Quit it, will you?
"A guitar..."
He's weird...
Hi!
-Ray, we're in trouble.
-Maho is.
-What? What's wrong?
-Uh-uh.
Hey, Yoshito...You tell
everything to my bro, huh?
Yoshito's dad appears
in nine dramas every week.
Yeah. I heard that from Maho.
Hey, Yoshito! This guy sang at
Dying Breed's secret live performance.
You know...My dad brought
an actress to my house last day...
-Who was it?
-Guess who...
I wonder what that was all about...
What's that?!
You mean we can't enter
the singing contest this year?!
What do you mean,
the Neighborhood Board Chair is mad?
We've been practicing like crazy every day.
Shut up, will you? You nitwit!
What's this all about?
Long time no see.
Nice to see you.
I was in the neighborhood,
so I decided to stop by.
You've been well?
Yeah...You look well too, Koyuki.
I heard from Kayo-chan.
You sang with Dying Breed?
That's awesome!
Yeah...Matt called me up.
Say, Koyuki...Haven't you grown a little?
Saito-san said the same thing to me.
You seem more grown up.
Hmm...Maybe it's because I'm being
forced to swim 3 kilometers every day.
I see...I haven't swum
for a while. I wish I could.
But I haven't got a swimsuit.
You don't swim?
Then tomorrow...
Shall we go to buy me a swimsuit?
"Summer Sale"
I wonder if it's a little too small.
Well, it had been quite a while...
I'm sorry if I said
anything I shouldn't...
-I broke up with my boyfriend...
-Huh?
No more gloomy subjects.
Say...Let's go swimming!
The public pool's closed today.
Oh, Yukio...A girl named Maho's
been calling for you.
What? If she calls again,
tell her I'll call her back later.
If you don't come, I'll go alone.
It's been a year since then...
Izumi-chan!
Oh, you're here, Koyuki!
"School Facility-No Trespassing"
-Hurray!
-If you talk too loudly, they'll catch us.
"School Facility-No Trespassing"
Do you understand? If you bend your knees
too much it'll slow you down.
Uh-huh...
Koyuki...
Do you like Maho-chan?
Huh?
I'm talking about the
singing contest last year.
I heard about it from Saito-san
a long time ago.
I have a feeling she likes you.
I guess I realized how I felt too late.
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
U-Uh...
"Fireworks"
"Fishing Hole"
All right. Thank you very much!
So, what did they want?
They want to hear Beck's demo tape.
Yahoo!
-Hey, watch out!
-Alright!
Anyway, thanks to Koyuki,
Beck's riding a big wave.
Music fans around the world
received shocking news today.
"Charismatic Singer Commits Suicide"
Music fans around the world
received shocking news today.
"Charismatic Singer Commits Suicide"
-Last night in New York,
-What?
Popular American singer Ms. Erica Blige
killed herself in her hotel room
with a pistol.
Ms. Erica, a charismatic singer
with many fans in Japan,
had CD sales of over 20 million worldwide.
According to a spokesman, her new album
was to be released in a few months...
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Sunfish are cute, aren't they?
"Live 13 'Ciel Bleu"'
I wonder if they're edible...